(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR
VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, PLACES,
LAWS AND NAMES ARE PURELY FICTIONAL.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THE WORK
CONTAINS SOME EXTREME LANGUAGE.
Squad 1's selection exam.
If I did well here,
I'm guaranteed to get into FS.
Such a cute scream.
Just like a small animal, Nekobana-kun.
And that's the match.
It's nice when you come at me
aggressively like a virgin,
but to beat me, you'll need
at least one hidden ball up your sleeve.
2 points.
5 points.
Those are your scores
from the written exam, aren't they?
Thank you very much.
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
Everyone, look at this.
Ta-da!
With this, I'm officially
a member of FS.
I didn't make it into Squad 1,
but I made them recognize my abilities.
Ah... good for you.
You traitor.
Such a traitor.
Surely a traitor.
A traitor, indeed.
Alright, I'm heading out.
Today's the enlistment ceremony.
Wait a minute, Jun.
The handover of Fumino,
you infiltrated FS to disrupt them
from the inside, right?
Of course.
There were new instructions
about the handover date as well.
The handover of Fumino Kotoyose
will take place on...
the Coming-of-Sex Day.
I need you warriors
to escort Fumino to the venue.
Coming-of-Sex Day?
It's an event on Seiran Island
to celebrate new adults,
whom the ban on lewd sex has been lifted
They dress up in
XXX-Crested Hakama or XXX Furisode,
and have sex all night long.
Heh, sounds like hell.
However, in recent years,
there has been a public outcry concerning
lewd exhibitionism and get pregnant morals.
Last year, an illegally copied of...
Hamedori-kun mascot went on a rampage.
So FS will also be mobilized for security.
We'll use the chaos to send Fumino off.
The operation's codename will be
"Hamedori-kun Mass Outbreak Hame."
MINOTSUKI ACADEMY
Stands.
Cumgratulations.
As of today,
you are officially members of FS.
Until now, I have been
strict with you as your instructor,
but from this moment on,
we are comrades who live by the same will.
Su su.
Therefore, I will guide you
even more strictly than before.
Be prepared.
- Sir, yes, sir!
- Sir, yes, sir, su!
As you all know,
we are fully committed to cracking down
on the Anti-Copulation Force.
First, I want you to look at this.
This is just a sample
created with a 3D printer.
It's the dick of the man believed to be
the leader of the Anti-Copulation Force.
So FS has the technology to replicate
a dick that has been inside a XXX.
Its size and hardness
were enough to blow Ikuko away.
A golden ratio woven by
the balance of the XXX and XXX.
Wow, it's so big...
Likes it's alive.
I've never seen anything like it.
This dignified presence...
Ah...
I'm about to cum just from touching it.
The woman inside me is throbbing with need.
Amazing.
A form so detailed
I can even feel XXX on my fingertips.
It's like an important cultural property
from a national museum.
On XXX-Auction,
it would go for no less than 1.9 billion.
The real one is even more amazing.
Huh?
If it were inserted into you,
you wouldn't be able to stay conscious.
Truly something that thrusts any
and all into a vortex of pleasure
A magical dick.
With this magical dick...
changing the world is no longer a dream.
What's with those eyes?
Such a creepy color.
As soon as the Coming-of-Sex day is over,
we will capture the Anti-Copulation Force
and the magical dick without fail.
Everyone, be prepared.
- Sir, yes, sir!
- Sir, yes, sir, su!
This is bad,
if we wait until it is over,
Fumino will be handed over
and it'll be too late.
What am I thinking?
Isn't that for the best?
We are sending Fumino home...
Now, I will announce the squad assignments.
Susuko and Schubert, you are in Squad 2.
Do your best maintaining public order.
Su.
Leave it to me.
Next, Nekobana.
Yes.
You will be Touka-sama's attendant.
The president's attendant?
You're XXX,
so you can't do any other work.
I have judged that you are capable of it.
I can't believe I'm being placed
next to the enemy leader right away.
If you're dissatisfied,
you can work under Rin.
What a lame belt.
Did you make it in home economics class?
Such a way of pulling it...
is not in my data.
Can you do it, Tachibana?
Yes, I'll do my best.
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
Getting close to the enemy leader,
this is my chance.
If I know what kind of person
the president is,
it'll be easier to read her.
Yes, this is FS.
Minotsuki Academy Student Council.
It's about time you apply the
Perverted Ordinance to the entire country.
With a name like Perverted Dick Law,
how about it?
I-I think it's a good name,
but we can't decide that on our own.
Ah, my dick is getting irritated.
We've been getting
a lot of complaints lately.
Let's rejoice in the fact that
we've been able to spread lewdness.
Spreading lewdness
is the supreme order from SHO, after all.
Yup.
But that's not all.
Sex is a very excellent means
of communication.
By looking at someone's face,
you can recognize them.
By shaking their hand,
you can become aware of them.
By exchanging words,
you can get to know them.
And...
by having sex, you can understand them.
Isn't that a very important thing?
Huh?
Hmm...
That's right.
Shall we skip work?
It reminds me
of when I became a sex adult.
Starting with a fresh mindset
and getting pregnant now!
and having my womb falling!
As the Coming-of-Sex day approaches,
everyone is starting with a fresh mindset.
The events on the island
are mainly organized by FS.
November's Lewd Conduct Facial Day
was also a huge success.
Lewd Conduct Facial?
As the islanders' duty,
we give thanks for the lewd conduct,
taking a xxx break and giving
facial instead.
Heh...
Senpai, are you not feeling well?
Eh? Ah, because there are a lot of people.
It's what's called sperm-sickness.
It's a common symptom for people
who haven't been on the island for long.
Let's move to a place with fresh air.
A wonderful place, isn't it?
I love this island.
I... see.
The people of Seiran Island
build deeper relationships through sex.
They can understand and respect others.
You don't seem to like
the island very much, senpai.
You were looking at the lewd sex
earlier with a pained expression.
That's...
My bad.
There must be things
you don't want to talk about.
But, senpai,
I want to understand you better too.
Nukitashi.
Excuse me.
Heave-ho.
Hey, where's Tachibana-kun?
He's at FS again today.
He got a sudden call.
I see, he's working hard.
Yeah, that's right. But...
Wata-chan, are you okay?
Oh, about what?
That weak XXX looking...
FS discipline committee chairwoman
is your childhood friend, right?
We have a hostile relationship with them.
Yeah, of course,
I don't want to fight with Rei-chan.
But I think she'll
understand one day that...
it's nice to have sex
with someone you like.
Because she often lends me
lovely shoujo manga with love stories.
And she's working hard at FS
for her little brother and sister.
If you say so,
then maybe we don't need to worry.
There are no bad people
among those with weak XXX.
Yeah, thank you both for worrying about me.
There, there.
It's strange.
Wata-chan is really like an older sister.
If she were a real older sister,
she should have boobs.
So this is the FS dorm.
Hmm, Tachibana?
Excuse me, I was called
by the student council president.
Hmm, I heard. Come in.
Excuse me.
Your atmosphere is different from usual.
It's my day off.
I can't be doing FS stuff on my day off.
I'm sleepy from staying up all night.
Do you watch this kind of stuff too, instructor?
That's...
My little brothers like it.
So I wanted to have
something in common with them.
Well... it's not like
I'm not into it.
How's your sister doing?
She is fine, thanks to you.
I see.
From now on,
you'll be receiving a scholarship.
It's the result of you
overcoming the harsh training.
You did well, Tachibana.
Ah, thank you very much.
So, where is
the student council president?
She's out shopping with
everyone from the dorm for later.
For later?
FRESH DICK WELCUM PARTY
This is...
Fresh Dick Welcum Party.
Well then,
I will now have the honor
of giving a toast.
Rei-chan, you're so stiff.
At a happy occasion like this,
only dicks should stay stiff.
Just cheers is enough. Cheers!
Cheers!
The food itself is simple,
but it's well-made.
Hey, hey, Nekobana-kun,
you really can't get hard?
I'm confident I can make you rock hard.
Ah, no, um...
Don't get cocky, Onabuta-san.
You always make them ejaculate
until they're all dried up!
And now, everyone, your attention please.
It's a silk hat.
A juice-squirting hat!
Voilà!
Bl-Blow-bohh!
Wow, you're so good at XXX, su.
Touka-chan is amazing.
She used to be hated by animals so much.
- Wow!
- As expected of the president!
I want to be the bird.
So the President can do magic tricks, too.
That's her true nature.
She just likes to make everyone happy.
Most of the school events are her ideas.
Hey, you newbie upperclassmen!
You guys should do something funny too.
Then I shall...
perform a magic trick where I make my
XXX point up without using my hands.
Yeah!
That's just getting a boner.
But if you can get a boner without
using your hands, I'd like to see that.
Eh? A boner without using my hands?
Yup, a boner!
Boner!
Boner! Boner! Boner!
Truly, deep down,
they're just a ridiculous bunch,
but they all accept the Perverted Ordinance,
and are enjoying their life here.
Hey!
What're you getting
all gloomy for, Banapai?
Are you okay? Want some breast milk?
Do your magic trick too.
A mysterious XXX magic where
it doesn't get bigger even if you rub it!
Stop it already.
Are you taking a break, senpai?
Yeah.
I didn't expect them to be this rowdy.
I'm sorry.
Everyone is lonely, so on days like these,
they tend to get rowdy.
All the FS members are students...
who are homeless or have family problems.
Rei had a XXX parent
and was sold to the island.
Ikuko is an orphan.
The food you guys made was delicious.
I'm glad it suited your taste.
The twins I fucked the other day,
identical faces,
but their cocks curved opposite ways.
Eh? Dick-metry?
- That's good luck.
The newbie, Susuko-san,
has a huge debt from her father.
And Nakamura-san joined FS
on his own to help his poor family.
Su su su.
Like this?
Something like this isn't in my data!
Same goes for everyone else.
We're living on scholarships from SHO.
In other words,
we cannot live if we defy SHO.
A group that can only
survive on Seiran Island.
That is us, the FS.
Ah, I haven't done
my homework for tomorrow.
I don't mind selling it to you.
Those donuts are delicious, aren't they?
This is a chikuwa.
One more drink!
I haven't had enough to drink.
That's just juice, though.
So this is FS.
Welcome back.
Are you okay, big brother?
You're late so I was getting worried.
Ah... my apologies
Look at this.
I've prepared for the operation
while you were gone, Tachibana-san.
This is Hinadori-kun, pako.
As expected, rock oysters
and vagina are best raw.
Heave-ho.
Hey, you.
A loli wouldn't say something like that.
I'm not a loli, though.
Sorry.
Leave me alone for a bit.
Does he want to masturbate?
They also call it fatigue-XXX relief.
Jun, can you hear me?
Yeah.
Did something happen at FS?
No, nothing.
I see.
You're a little hard to understand,
but you're kind.
I thought this might happen.
That you wouldn't be able to see
FS the same way as before.
But I don't think
that's necessarily a bad thing.
So if you're having a hard time,
this operation...
No need for that!
The Perverted Ordinance must be crushed.
We are NLNS, rebels against lewd sex.
FS is our enemy.
Jun.
I understand. But please don't overdo it.
Cumgratulations on becoming an sex adult.
What will you do for your first lewd sex?
As expected, for my first time...
With gratitude to my parents, I'll go for...
the Peni-Pan Queen's reverse XXX!
Yeah!
Such filial piety!
The future of Japan is bright.
Hame!
The Coming-of-Sex day
is an important event on Seiran Island.
All units, dedicate yourselves to security.
- Sir, yes, sir!
- Sir, yes, sir, su!
Just in case, be on the lookout
for the Anti-Copulation Force.
Nekobana and Susuko, you're a two-man cell.
Watch the back mountain's C3 area.
Roger, su!
Roger!
Wait, Nekobana.
Take this, just in case.
A handgun.
Same as yours.
It's just my hand-me-down.
Are you sure?
It's a recognition of your efforts.
Work even harder,
for your sister's sake too.
Good for you, Banapai!
Thank you very much.
This is fine.
Using this trust,
I will crush the ordinance for sure.
This is NULL Base.
All units, report your status.
Security around the point is tight.
But a few Hamedori-kun
have also appeared.
We can do this.
The plan is to blend in
with the new adults and send Fumino off.
We can also steal a boat.
I can do it anytime.
Wata-chan, even if juvenile law applies...
But I'm not a loli!
We're ready to go too.
When the chance comes,
we'll rush to the port and board the boat.
Fumino-chan, don't get thrown off.
To think you can even
make something like this.
The 3D printer is amazing.
It's thanks to Tachibana-san.
Tachibana-san.
We've entrusted our fate to you.
Bana-san, what if
the Anti-Copulation Force really shows up?
If we catch the magical dick...
we might get a monetary bonus!
Then I could pay off the debt
that my shitty... my father left.
Big brother, preparations are complete.
We can go anytime.
Roger.
Didn't you hear
a noise over there just now?
Ah, really?
I'll go check.
Stay on standby.
Be careful.
Let's do this!
Let's go!
This is Nekobana.
I've found
the Anti-Copulation Force at point C3.
Requesting backup.
What?
Alright, point C3.
Yes.
I'll send backup right away.
We won! With this, the ordinance...
You did well, Tachibana.
A group that can only
survive on Seiran Island.
That is us, the FS.
You did well, Tachibana.
This is Nekobana.
What's wrong?
It's a diversion.
W-What?
It was an enemy diversion to trick us.
The main body of the Anti-Copulation Force
seems to be at point B5.
The Anti-Copulation Force is at B5.
Roger.
Great job.
Tachibana? Hey, Tachibana.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I will continue security.
Sorry.
The operation is cancelled.
Eh?
Jun...
What do you mean cancelled?
Tachibana-san...
Everyone, retreat immediately.
Big brother, why?
Sorry.